BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6828: Allied Employers Inc. and UFCW, 1974-1994 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Spokane food stores and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1974-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1974 and expires on 6/1/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 2: Spokane food stores and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1974-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 6/2/1974 and expires on 6/28/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 3: Spokane food stores and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 6/29/1975 and expires on 6/25/1978. Covers 1200 workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 4: Spokane food stores and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/25/1978 and expires on 10/27/1981. Covers 1250 workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 5: Spokane food stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 1439, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/28/1981 and expires on 10/30/1984. Covers 1435 workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 6: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 1439 Memorandum, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1984 and expires on 10/3/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 7: Food Giant, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 442, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 5/20/1984 and expires on 11/29/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Georgia; Alabama
    - Item 8: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 1439, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1984 and expires on 10/3/1987. Covers 1100 workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 9: Big Star and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 442, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1985 and expires on 11/28/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers.
    - Item 10: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1987 and expires on 10/6/1990. Covers 1422 workers in Spokane, WA
    - Item 11: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Item 12: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1439, 1990-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/7/1990 and expires on 1/1/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Spokane, WA
  - Code no.6834: Great A & P Tea Co. and UFCW, 1973-1994 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10, 1973-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 6/10/1973 and expires on 10/7/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 6/21/1974 and expires on 6/19/1976. Covers 2300 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10 Memorandum, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1974 and expires on 6/19/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 10/20/1976 and expires on 6/23/1979. Covers 1800 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 5: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10 Memorandum, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Item 6: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 10, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 6/24/1979 and expires on 6/27/1982. Covers 2000 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 7: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 9/15/1985 and expires on 9/24/1988. Covers 1500 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 8: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 9/29/1991 and expires on 10/1/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
  - Code no.6842: Eisner Food Stores and UFCW, 1973-1991 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595 Memorandum, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 12/30/1973 and expires on 12/30/1974. Covers an unknown number of workers in Illinois
    - Item 2: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595 Memorandum, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1974 and expires on 9/30/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Illinois
    - Item 3: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Item 4: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595 Addendum, 1975-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/3/1975 and expires on 9/30/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Illinois
    - Item 5: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595 Addendum, 1975-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/3/1975 and expires on 8/2/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Illinois
    - Item 6: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/3/1976 and expires on 10/20/1979. Covers 931 workers in Illinois
    - Item 7: Eisner Food Stores and United Retail Workers, Local 595, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/21/1979 and expires on 10/16/1982. Covers 1400 workers in Illinois
    - Item 8: Eisner Food Stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 881, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/14/1984 and expires on 10/10/1987. Covers 1000 workers in Illinois
    - Item 9: Eisner Food Stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 881, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/14/1984 and expires on 10/10/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Illinois
    - Item 10: Eisner Food Stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 881, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/9/1988 and expires on 10/5/1991. Covers 900 workers in Illinois
  - Code no.6846: Colonial Stores Inc. /Big Star and UFCW, 1974-1989 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Big Star and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 204, 1983-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 7/24/1983 and expires on 4/27/1987. Covers 2100 workers in Norht Carolina; Soouth Carolina; Georgia
    - Item 2: Big Star and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 204, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/24/1986 and expires on 7/28/1989. Covers 2150 workers in Norht Carolina; Soouth Carolina; Georgia
    - Item 3: Colonial Stores Incorporated and Retail Clerks, AFL-CIO, Local 204, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 10/6/1974 and expires on 10/3/1976. Covers 1350 workers in Norht Carolina
    - Item 4: Colonial Stores Incorporated and Retail Clerks, AFL-CIO, Local 204, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 10/3/1976 and expires on 10/6/1979. Covers 1155 workers in Norht Carolina
    - Item 5: Colonial Stores Group and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 204, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 10/7/1979 and expires on 10/10/1982. Covers 1773 workers in Norht Carolina
  - Code no.6848: Rice Food Market and Retail Clerks, 1971-1981 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Rice Food Markets, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 455, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 10/3/1971 and expires on 9/7/1974. Covers an unknown number of workers in Harris Co., TX; Galveston Co., TX; Montgomery Co., TX
    - Item 2: Grocery stores and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 455, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/7/1975 and expires on 9/9/1978. Covers 622 workers in Harris Co., TX; Galveston Co., TX; Montgomery Co., TX
    - Item 3: Rice Food Markets, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 455, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/10/1978 and expires on 10/22/1981. Covers 800 workers in Harris Co., TX; Galveston Co., TX; Montgomery Co., TX; Walker Co., TX
  - Code no.6850: Milgram Food Stores Inc. and Retail Clerks, 1974-1976 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Milgram Food Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union, AFL- CIO, Local 782, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1974 and expires on 5/8/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jackson Co., MO; Clay Co., MO; Platte Co., MO; Cass Co., MO; Johnson Co.; KS; Wyandotte Co., KS
  - Code no.6852: Safeway Stores Inc., Ice Cream Dept. and IBT, 1974-1986 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Safeway Stores, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Locals 745, 886, 523, 878, 577 and 968, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/2/1974 and expires on 6/1/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Amarillo, TX; Dallas, TX; Oklahoma City, OK; Little Rock, AR; Searcy, AR
    - Item 2: Safeway Stores, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Locals 745, 886, 523, 878, 577, 968, 941 and 492, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/5/1977 and expires on 6/7/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Dallas, TX; El Paso, TX; Albuquerque, NM; Oklahoma City, OK; Little Rock, AR; Searcy, AR
    - Item 3: Ice Cream Department, Safeway Stores, Incorporated and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 941, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 5/3/1982 and expires on 5/6/1985. Covers an unknown number of workers in El Paso, TX
    - Item 4: Safeway Stores, Inc. Ice Cream Department and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 745, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/12/1983 and expires on 6/14/1986. Covers 30 workers in Dallas, TX
    - Item 5: Safeway Stores, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 745, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/19/1983 and expires on 6/21/1986. Covers 120 workers in Dallas, TX
    - Item 6: Safeway Stores, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 968, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 4/3/1983 and expires on 4/5/1986. Covers 28 workers in Houston, TX
    - Item 7: Safeway Stores, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 886, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/19/1983 and expires on 6/21/1986. Covers 33 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
    - Item 8: Safeway Stores, Inc. Ice Cream Department and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 878, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/5/1983 and expires on 6/7/1986. Covers 8 workers in Little Rock, AR
    - Item 9: Safeway Stores, Inc. Ice Cream Department and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 886, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/12/1983 and expires on 6/14/1986. Covers 12 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
  - Code no.6853: Jewel Food Stores Division of Jewel Co. Inc. and IBT, 1973-1982 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Jewel Food Stores Division of Jewel Companies, Inc. and Chicago Truck Drivers, Helpers, and Warehouse Workers Union, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1973 and expires on 3/31/1976. Covers 1200 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: Jewel Food Stores Division of Jewel Companies, Inc. and Chicago Truck Drivers, Helpers, and Warehouse Workers Union, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1976 and expires on 3/31/1979. Covers 300 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Jewel Food Stores Division of Jewel Companies, Inc. and Chicago Truck Drivers, Helpers, and Warehouse Workers Union, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1979 and expires on 3/31/1982. Covers 700 workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6854: Great A & P Tea Co., Louisville Unit and American Meat Cutters and Butcher Workers, 1974-1983 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Louisville Division and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Locals 99, 227, 405 and 452, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/24/1974 and expires on 10/29/1977. Covers 1650 workers in Tennessee; Inidiana; Kentucky
    - Item 2: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Indianapolis/Louisville Division and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 227, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/30/1977 and expires on 10/25/1980. Covers 1800 workers in Inidiana; Kentucky
    - Item 3: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Louisville Division and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 227, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/26/1980 and expires on 10/29/1983. Covers 900 workers in Tennessee; Inidiana; Kentucky
  - Code no.6856: I-A Supermarkets (Kroger, A & P, Big Star, Food Giant, Casey's) and UFCW, 1975-1987 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Big Apple Super Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 442, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 1/5/1975 and expires on 1/21/1978. Covers 275 workers in Georgia; Alabama; Chattanooga, TN
    - Item 2: The Kroger Co. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 442, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 1/22/1978 and expires on 1/24/1981. Covers an unknown number of workers in Georgia; North Augusta, SC; Opelika, AL
    - Item 3: The Kroger Co. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 442, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 1/25/1981 and expires on 5/19/1984. Covers an unknown number of workers in Georgia; North Augusta, SC; Opelika, AL; Auburn, AL
    - Item 4: The Kroger Co. - Atlanta Division and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 442 Memorandum, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/20/1984 and expires on 11/28/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers.
    - Item 5: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 442 Memorandum, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Item 6: Casey's Big Buy and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 442, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1984 and expires on 11/28/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cedartown, GA; Cave Springs, GA; Rockmart, GA
  - Code no.6859: Master Food & Liquor Agreement (Food & liquor Employees) and Retail Clerks, 1974-1989 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 17, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1974 and expires on 2/26/1977. Covers 1025 workers in Butte Co., CA; Glenn Co. CA; Plumas Co., CA; Colusa Co., CA; Sierra Co., CA; Yuba Co., CA; Sutter Co., CA; Lassen Co., CA; Nevada Co. CA
    - Item 2: Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 17, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 2/27/1977 and expires on 2/29/1980. Covers 1200 workers in Butte Co., CA; Glenn Co. CA; Plumas Co., CA; Colusa Co., CA; Sierra Co., CA; Yuba Co., CA; Sutter Co., CA; Lassen Co., CA; Nevada Co. CA
    - Item 3: Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 17, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 2/29/1980 and expires on 2/28/1983. Covers 1250 workers in Butte Co., CA; Glenn Co. CA; Plumas Co., CA; Colusa Co., CA; Sierra Co., CA; Yuba Co., CA; Sutter Co., CA; Lassen Co., CA; Nevada Co. CA
    - Item 4: Food and Liquor Employers and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 17R, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1983 and expires on 2/28/1986. Covers 900 workers in Butte Co., CA; Glenn Co. CA; Plumas Co., CA; Colusa Co., CA; Sierra Co., CA; Yuba Co., CA; Sutter Co., CA; Lassen Co., CA; Nevada Co. CA
    - Item 5: Food Employers and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 916, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1986 and expires on 2/28/1989. Covers 1600 workers in Butte Co., CA; Glenn Co. CA; Plumas Co., CA; Colusa Co., CA; Sierra Co., CA; Yuba Co., CA; Sutter Co., CA; Lassen Co., CA; Nevada Co. CA; Modoc Co., CA; Shasta Co., CA; Siskiyou
  - Code no.6861: Food Mart Division of Waldbaum Inc. and UFCW, 1976-1988 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: The Food Mart Division of Waldbaum, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Locals 33 and 371, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 5/2/1976 and expires on 4/7/1979. Covers 1500 workers in Masachusetts; Connecticut
    - Item 2: Food Mart/Waldbaum, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Locals 33 and 371 Memorandum, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1976 and expires on 1/1/1979. Covers an unknown number of workers in Masachusetts; Connecticut
    - Item 3: Food Mart/Waldbaum Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 371 Memorandum, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1985 and expires on 6/18/1988. Covers 4000 workers in Masachusetts; Connecticut
  - Code no.6862: Fry's Food Stores of Arizona Inc. and Retail Clerks, 1974-1983 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Fry's Food Stores of Arizona, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 99, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 8/5/1974 and expires on 7/31/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Arizona
    - Item 2: Fry's Food Stores of Arizona, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 99, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1977 and expires on 8/3/1980. Covers 990 workers in Arizona
    - Item 3: Fry's Food Stores of Arizona, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 99 Memorandum, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1980 and expires on 7/1/1983. Covers 900 workers in Arizona
  - Code no.6863: Food & Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks, 1977-1989 (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Independent Grocers and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 2/27/1977 and expires on 2/29/1980. Covers 1303 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 2: Independent Grocers and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 588 Memorandum, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1980 and expires on 2/28/1983. Covers 1900 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 3: Corti Brothers and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/2/1986 and expires on 4/30/1989. Covers an unknown number of workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 4: Bel Air Markets and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 173, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1986 and expires on 4/30/1989. Covers an unknown number of workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA; San Joaquin Co. CA